hi everyone in this video I'm gonna
大家好，我要解释一下这段视频中的代表通话并显示
explain what delegate call is and show
you how to use it
您如何使用它委托调用是一个低级功能
delegate call is a low-level function
similar to call method and it's used to
类似于调用方法，它用于调用我要调用的所有合约
call all the contracts I like to call
method when delegate call is used inside
在联系日之内使用委托呼叫来调用合同时的方法
contact day to call contract be contract
beads code is run inside a context so
珠子代码在上下文中运行，所以这意味着在合同内部
what this means is that inside contract
be storage will refer to contract a
被存储将参考签约存储消息，发件人将参考
storage message the sender will refer to
the caller who called contract day and
呼叫合同日和消息狗值的呼叫者将是
message dog value will be the value that
was sent to contract day now once you
在您将智能合约部署到
deploy a smart contract onto the
blockchain you can't change the code of
区块链，您无法更改该合约的代码
that contract
however using delegate call you're able
但是，即使您使用委托通话，您也可以更新合同
to update the contract even though you
cannot change any of the code inside it
假设有两个合同，则无法更改其中的任何代码
suppose that there are two contracts
contract a and contract e inside
合约a内的合约a和合约e我们有一个称为
contract a we have a function called
increment so when you call the function
增量，因此当您在合同内部调用函数增量时，它会调用
increment inside contract a it calls
another function also called increment
合约B内部的另一个函数也称为增量，现在假设爱丽丝
inside contract B now suppose Alice
calls a function increment inside
在合约a内调用函数增量并在其中发送一米
contract a and sends one meter inside
contract a message sender will equal to
签约消息发件人将等于爱丽丝的地址和消息点
the address of Alice and message dot
value will equal to one ether and the
值将等于一个以太，并且状态变量X的值等于
value of the state variable X is equal
to zero from contract a it calls the
从合约a到零，它调用内部的函数增量
function increment which is inside
contract be inside contract the message
合同在合同内，消息发件人将等于合同a，因为
sender will equal to contract a since
contract a is the address that called
合同a是称为合同B消息点值的地址
contract B message dot value will be
zero either since contract a do not send
零，因为合约a不向合约B发送任何以太币，而初始合约
any ether to contract B and the initial
value of the state variable X will be
状态变量X的值将等于零函数增量
equal to zero the function increment
updates the state variable X by one now
现在假设我们在内部使用委托调用来更新状态变量X
suppose that we use delegate call inside
contract a to call function increment
合约a再次调用合约B内的函数增量是
inside contract B is again cause of
Chanin comment inside contract a and
Chanin在合同a中发表评论，并发送与先前相同的Juanita
sends Juanita same as the previous
example message the sender will be Alice
示例消息，发件人将是爱丽丝，消息狗的值将是一米
and message dog value will be one meter
and the state variable X will be equal
状态变量X从合同a等于0，它称为
to zero from contract a it calls the
function increment inside contract be
合同中的函数增量现在使用委托调用，这与
using delegate call now unlike the
previous example message the sender will
上一个示例消息，发件人将是Alice消息的终止值将是
be Alice message stop value will be
equal to one Eater and the initial state
等于一个Eater，状态变量X的初始状态将等于
of the state variable X will be equal to
zero so you can already see that using
零，因此您已经看到使用委托呼叫消息，发件人和
delegate call message the sender and
message stop value is preserved to the
消息停止值保留为原始值现在让我们看看
original values now let's see what
happens to the state variable when the
当执行合同B内的代码时，状态变量发生在状态变量上
code inside contract B is executed it
does not change the state variable
不会更改合约B内的状态变量和状态变量
inside contract B and the state variable
X inside contract a not inside contract
合同内的X而不是合同B内的X已更新，所以这里发生的是
B is updated so what's happening here is
that delegate call runs the code inside
该委托调用使用存储消息在合同内运行代码
contract be using the storage message
dot sender and message dot value of
点发件人和合同的消息点值a委托调用如何
contract a so how is delegate call
useful well using delegate call you can
使用委托调用很有用，您可以编写可升级合同，我该怎么办
write upgradeable contracts what do I
mean by this
因此，假设合同a和合同B
suppose that contract a and contract B
are already deployed on the blockchain
已经部署在区块链上，这意味着您将无法
so this means that you won't be able to
change the code inside either contract a
更改合同a内的代码或更改合同a内的代码
or contract be inside contract a we
store two state variables U and named X
存储两个状态变量U并命名为X以及合约B的地址和
and the address of contract B and the
function increment uses the delegate
函数增量使用委托调用方法来调用合约B，所以让我们
call method to call contract B so let's
say that Alice calls the function
说爱丽丝将合同内的功能增量称为合同
increment inside contract a contract
they would call the increment
他们会调用合同的增量功能
functioning of contract be using
delegate call the code inside contract B
委托调用合同B中的代码被执行，并且状态变量为
is executed and the state variable of
contract a is updated now imagine we
现在更新了合同a，假设我们将合同的版本2命名为
have a version 2 of contract be named
be two and let's say that inside
是两个，假设在合约内部，我们有一个函数
contract a we have a function where we
could update the address of contract B
可以更新合同B的地址，以便此B变量现在保存
so that this B variable now holds the
address or contract B - and now let's
地址或合同B-现在让我们看看当现在导致
see what happens when now has caused a
function increment inside contract a
合约内的函数增量再次如此，就像在Alice调用之前
again so like before Alice calls the
function increment
现在函数增加，因为地址B现在指向
now since the address B now points to
contract B - when Alice called the
合同B-当爱丽丝调用增量函数时，它调用了一个函数
increment function it called a function
increment inside contract B to the code
将合同B内部的增量增加到合同B内部的代码-并执行
inside contract B - is executed and the
state variable inside contract a is
合同a中的状态变量已更新，通知我们能够
updated notice that we were able to
change how the state variable X is
更改状态变量X在代理调用时如何使用委托调用进行更新
updated using delegate call when the
address be pointed to contract B it
指向合同B的地址将状态变量X递增1
incremented the state variable X by 1
but after we updated the address of B to
但是在我们更新了B的地址以指向联系人B之后-我们能够
point to contact B - we were able to
increment the state variable X by 2 so
将状态变量X加2，所以这是如何使用
this is the idea of how to use the
legate called update your contract even
即使您无法更改其中的代码，也被称为更新您的合同的代表
though you cannot change the code inside
the contract to show how all of this
合同，以使用我们首先要介绍的代码来展示所有这些工作原理
works using code we're going to first
declare some state variables for this
在此示例中声明一些状态变量，我们将声明一个状态
example we're gonna declare a state
variable called num sender and value for
在本例中，我们将创建一个名为num sender和value的变量
this example we're gonna create a
function called set bars and inside this
称为设置栏的函数，该函数内部将使用委托调用
function will use a delegate call to
call contract B now the function set
调用合约B，现在功能设置栏将接受两个参数
bars is going to take two arguments
address subcontract B and some number
地址分包合同B和我们将在此示例中使用的一些数字
that we're going to use for this example
and since we're going to send some meter
而且由于我们要向该功能发送一些仪表，所以我们还将
to this function we're also going to
declare this as payable the way you use
将其声明为应付款，您使用委托调用的方式类似于该调用
delegate call is similar to the call
method inside the delegate call function
委托调用函数中的方法，您可以使用bi编码调用该函数
you call the function a bi encode with
signature inside a bi dot encode with
双点编码内的签名，您首先要在函数中传递签名
signature you first pass in the function
signature of the function that we're
我们将要调用的函数的签名，因此在合同内我们
going to call so inside contract the we
later define a function called set bars
稍后定义一个称为设置栏的函数，它将结束您的任务，因此在这里
that's going to take a you end so here
we're passing
我们将其作为函数签名传递给集合
as a function signature and to the set
bars function that we're gonna call
我们将在内部调用的Bar函数，称为Jack B，我们将向前
inside called Jack B we're gonna forward
the input num like call method delegate
输入num类似于调用方法委托调用，返回两个输出布尔值
call returns two outputs a boolean value
called success that returns true if the
称为成功，如果执行的函数没有任何错误，则返回true；并且
function executed without any errors and
the output of the function that was
以字节为单位调用的函数的输出，但在此示例中，我们
called in bytes but for this example we
don't need to worry about the output of
不必担心合同B内部下一个委托调用的输出
delegate call next inside contract B we
first need to declare the state
首先需要声明状态变量，并且这些状态变量必须
variables and these state variable must
be in the exact same order as contract a
与合同a的顺序完全相同，因此如果您要更改合同的顺序
so if you were to change the order of
the state variables then when the code
状态变量，那么当合约B中的代码运行时，它会混乱
inside contract B is run it would mess
up the state variables inside contract a
合同内部的状态变量，因此记住
so it's important to remember to have
the exact same state variable as
与合同a完全相同的状态变量，顺序相同
contract a in the same order the
function set bars is going to take a
功能集栏将占用您输入的功能，
youant as input inside the function will
capture the input the color of the
捕获输入的合同颜色和发送到的值
contract and the value that was sent to
the contract into the state variables
将合同转换为状态变量，现在我们可以部署合同了
now we're ready to deploy the contracts
and see a demo so here are deployed
并查看一个演示，因此这里部署了合同a和合同B，现在我们
contract a and contract B and now we're
gonna call the function set bars on
会调用合约a上的函数集吧，这会改变
contract a and that should change the
state variable inside contract a but
合约a内的状态变量，但对状态变量没有影响
have no effect on the state variables
inside contact B so I'm gonna copy the
内部联系人B，所以我要复制合同B的地址，我们将
address of contract B and we're gonna
call a set bars function so I'm going to
调用set bar函数，所以我将在此处通过传递数字来复制该函数
copy that this here passing the number
one two three and we're gonna send one
一二三，我们要么寄一个
either
so after the function was called the NAM
因此，在将该函数称为contact的NAM状态变量之后，
state variable of contact they should
now be one two three the sender should
现在是一二三，发件人应该是我们帐户的地址，
be the address of our account and the
value should be one meter and the state
值应为一米，合同B的状态变量应不为
variables of contract B should have not
changed at all so next I want to show
完全改变了，所以接下来我想向您展示如何升级合约
you how to upgrade contract a that is
already deployed first we'll create a
首先已经部署完毕，我们将创建合同B的新版本，因此我们将
new version of contract B so we're gonna
copy contract B paste it here and then
复制合同B，将其粘贴到此处，然后将其重命名为合同b2。
rename it as contract b2 now remember
that the layout of the state variables
状态变量的布局必须与合同a相同，并且
have to be the same as contract a and
inside the function step bars we'll
在功能步骤栏中，我们将输入乘以2，然后存储
multiply the input by two and then store
the result so here I have newly deployed
结果，因此在这里我新部署了合同b2，合同a仍然是
contract b2 and contract a is still the
same contract from the previous demo and
与上一个演示相同的合同，我们将在其中调用功能集栏
we'll call the function set bars inside
contract a passing in the address of
签约合同b2的地址中的传球，这就是您的乘数
contract b2 so that's your multiplier
input by 2 and store the result inside
输入2并将结果存储在合同中a我要复制地址
contract a I'm going to copy the address
of contract V to paste it in here and
合同V的名称将其粘贴到此处，并使用相同的输入1 2 3进行调用，并且
call it with the same input 1 2 3 and
this time you'll pass 2 liters so now
这次您将通过2升，因此自我们通过1 2 3以来，现在的数量为246
the num to be 246 since we passed 1 2 3
which was x to the center should still
到中心的x值应该仍然相同，并且值现在应该是
be the same and the values should now be
to eaters
食者，所以总之委托调用运行
so in summary delegate call runs the
code of Kali using the colors context
使用颜色上下文的Kali代码，Kali的状态变量必须为
the state variables of the Kali must be
the same as the color and you can use
与颜色相同，您可以使用委托调用来更好地更新合同
delegate call to update contracts well
that's all I got for this video if you
如果您有任何疑问或费用，这就是我为这部影片所获得的一切
have any questions or fee
but let me know in the comments below
但请在下面的评论中让我知道您度过了一个美好的夜晚，很快我会再见
have a good night and I'll see you soon
in the next video
在下一个视频中